Holy Mary , Mother of God , pray for us sinners now
and at the hour of our death . Amen .
Hail Mary , full of grace , the Lord is with thee .
Blessed art thou amongst women ...
Put them there .
Hail Mary , full of grace , the Lord is with thee .
Blessed art thou amongst women and blessed is the fruit of thy womb , Jesus .
- What are you doing ? - I 'm sorry .
- Hurry up and finish ! Come on ! - I 'm coming .
I 'm coming .
Good !
Very good .
- And you ? - Yes .
- Get them up ! - What 's wrong with you ?
Stop it ! Do you want it to work or not ?
Valeria Hernandez .
Best of luck , sweetheart .
- Gotcha ! - What ?
What ?
- You smell like cigarettes . - No .
Yeah , right .
Fucking chain-smoker .
What 's up ?
What ?
Is that it ?
Give it to me .
- Before or after dinner ? - What do you mean ? No way !
No way ...
Yes !
Do you like it ?
What a silly question . We only like handmade cribs .
Are you going to make it ?
Yes , I 've already started .
Wouldn 't you rather buy it ?
No . She has already started it .
This one is lovely !
Isn 't it cute ?
A gift from Grandma .
Thanks , Norma , but it 's not my style ...
Miss !
- Thanks , Mom . - Excuse me ! Miss !
Don 't let her buy it .
- But she is so excited . - I know , but it is awful .
Yeah .
We will only use it when she comes to visit .
You 're twelve weeks . Now it 's official .
So , how are you feeling ?
She has trouble sleeping .
It 's all part of the excitement .
Okay , let 's begin .
Okay .
Good .
That 's it .
I 've lost my appetite a bit .
Are you still doing carpentry and using those chemicals ?
- What do you think , doc ? - Those are strong chemicals .
I recommend that you stop , at least for the next few months .
What 's up ?
I 'm ready .
I 'll just finish this and get ready .
- How is the cradle coming along ? - Fine .
As soon as I finish it , I 'll start with the baby 's room .
Good-bye workshop .
Hurry up .
This song is dedicated to the most valuable
treasure we have in Mexico .
Today , on their day , we congratulate all mothers .
- How much ? - 120 pesos , whichever you like .
Thanks .
We were going to come empty-handed on Mother 's Day !
We suck !
- Hi , Dad . - You forgot your keys .
Did you lose them again ?
- Hello , Luis . - Come in .
Happy Mother 's Day , Mom .
Congratulations to you too .
What did I tell you ?
Our Virgin performed a miracle for you .
- Congratulations , Maricarmen . - Thanks .
Hi , sis !
Happy Mother 's Day .
Really , Vero ? Congratulate her too .
Congratulations .
Your clock was ticking
Are you happy ?
Delighted .
Funny , you 're not a kid person .
How could she not be ?
Has she ever carried her nephew and niece ?
Yes , I have , haven 't I , Pao ?
I was just saying .
You 're wrong . She was not going to be a spinster like your aunt .
- Mom ! - It 's true !
Don 't even remind me of the fucking party .
She is angry because she can 't get anyone to babysit the children .
It pisses me off ! I can never go anywhere .
I can babysit them .
What ?
I don 't know if you can handle this .
Come on , Mom !
What happened with the neighbor could happen again .
What neighbor ?
A neighbor who used to ask us to babysit her child .
You really never told Raul about that ?
- Shall I tell you ? - Vero , please !
- Let her tell me . - It 's okay .
We used to babysit for this neighbor .
One day , it 's just the two of us and I say , " I 'll be right back ,
I 'm going to the store , keep an eye on him . "
As I am going down the stairs , she comes running and says ,
" Will you get me a muffin ? "
At that moment , the baby slips out of her arms
and rolls down the stairs , one step after another , and he lands by my feet .
And she just kept staring at him .
- Did he get hurt ? - No .
It was an accident .
I 've noticed he 's a little weird .
I think he is a bit slow .
Then don 't go to the party , what the fuck do I care ?
Chill out !
Come on , Vero .
Let her babysit the children . It will be like a training , dear .
- It 's you , aunt ! - Don 't be scared . Come .
Don 't mind them .
They only want to piss you off .
What 's wrong ?
No , no , no .
We are not going to be like that .
They were just messing around .
Bye !
Valeria ?
- Hello , Raul ! - Octavia , what are you doing here ?
I live around here , dude .
Were you at your parents ' ?
Yes . It 's Mother 's Day .
Since when do you care ?
Hold on , jerk !
Are you okay ?
Yes .
You look different .
It 's been many years since we 've seen each other , hasn 't it ?
If you want to drop by someday ...
Cool .
Take care .
She hasn 't changed a bit .
No !
Raul !
A woman jumped off ! She broke her legs and ...
I saw her ! She 's on the ground and ...
Her body is broken ! She 's down there !
Where ?
There ! She jumped off from there !
- I swear ! - I can 't see anything .
I saw her , I swear ! She jumped off !
- She was there ! - But where ?
- Good morning . - Hello .
You lost six pounds .
You have symptoms of anemia .
I don 't want to scare you ,
but if you go on like this , your pregnancy could be at risk .
Just calm down .
Tell me , how 's the baby 's room going ?
Damn it !
What is it ?
Sorry .
Doesn 't it creep you out ?
What if we hurt the baby ?
But there 's no baby yet .
Of course there is !
Of course there 's a baby !
Raul !
What were you doing outside ?
I think someone broke into the house .
What are you talking about ?
What is going on ?
There was a knock on the door .
Okay ...
I opened it but no one was there .
So I went downstairs to check if anyone was there and ...
They closed ... They closed the door on me !
- Calm down ... - How can I calm down ?
- Val ... - Are you listening to me ?
Do you see anyone here ?
Look around !
There , look .
You left the window open .
It was the wind .
Hey , are you okay ?
Do you mind if I go back to bed ?
No .
Thanks for bringing me here , Aunt .
Just don 't tell your mother , huh ?
She looks for reasons to get hysterical .
This is just between us .
Look , my friends .
Are you coming ?
I 'll wait for you here .
- What do you want ? - Chabelita is here ...
Hi , Chabela !
Look at this fancy Nancy !
I can hardly recognize you .
When was the last time we saw each other ?
When your head was shaved .
Come in .
- How far along are you ? - Almost five months .
I cut , I cancel , I renounce , I cauterize .
You wanted it ?
Come see this .
You 've got the spider .
It 's a weaver .
This one is a mother , but also a predator .
She had you wrapped tightly in her cobweb . Look .
Here you can see a house , but it 's also a prison .
Don 't worry .
In a few days you 'll feel better .
If you feel bad again , give me a call .
There 's another way to fix this , but ...
Can 't we try it now ?
No . I don 't do such dark stuff .
Ask your aunt .
You 'll be all right . You 'll see .
Vale ...
Cut it out !
- Fuck , cut it out ! - What is this bullshit ?
- Cut it out ! - I don 't like it !
No , don 't !
- Surrender ! - No way !
Your belly , your belly !
You gained nine pounds Valeria , bravo !
Do you want to know ?
Yes !
It 's a girl .
You have a 24-week-old little princess .
We 're having a girl !
Look at her .
See ?
- This is her head . - I see it !
- There ! - Her legs .
- And that , in the middle ? - Her little hand .
- It 's her fist , isn 't it ? - Yes .
- Where ? - There !
- She 's moving . - Look ! There she is !
Let 's measure her head .
Where ?
Look ! Look at her !
What happened ?
- What happened ? What happened ? - It 's broken !
- What 's broken ? - My foot !
How ... ? Valeria !
Valeria , listen ! Valeria ! Val , Val !
Hey , I 'm here !
It was a dream . Just a dream .
It hurts a lot .
It was a fucking cramp .
Hey , breathe .
It will pass . Breathe .
You 're fine ! Look !
Your foot is fine .
It 's okay .
Hot , cold . You must alternate them . You get it , right ?
Put it in .
It 's hot .
You are tense when you are sleeping .
It didn 't feel like a dream . It hurt a lot .
You 're not going to stick with that idea , are you ?
You set your mind on something and you go round and round it .
You aren 't even sleeping well anymore .
I got to go to work .
Relax .
Sixty , sixty-one ,
sixty-two , sixty-three ,
sixty-four , sixty-five ,
sixty-six .
Valeria Hernandez , the Little Mermaid !
Here , my love .
Take your prize , Little Mermaid . You did it .
Shut up or I 'll call the police , you faggots !
You shut up , snitch ! Screw you !
I 'm the only faggot here , bitch !
Just tell her .
If you don 't tell her , someone else will .
And it will be worse .
Octavia ?
What the fuck , you jerk !
Does it hurt again ?
It 's because of that stupid game .
You always try to please those jerks .
In a few days we 'll be far away from this damn city .
What ?
No way , Valeria . Are you having doubts ?
I don 't want to leave my family .
Not now .
Months go by and I still can 't believe what happened to your brother .
I 'm considering applying for college , like him .
You ? Are you serious ?
Why didn 't you tell me ?
I 've only been thinking about it for a couple of days .
My mom was so proud of him .
All right .
If that 's what you want , that 's cool .
It 's just a few years , right ?
I guess ...
Fucking nerd !
The first college student of the family .
Run ! Run !
I don 't like domestication !
Harder ! Hit it !
Good . Hit it ! Come on .
That 's it !
Harder ! That 's it !
Come on , come on . Hit it !
Hit it , hit it ! Hold on , hold on .
See you Friday , don 't be late .
Cool .
I 'm all sweaty .
You 're all right .
Long time no see !
I thought you hated me .
No .
Just a little bit .
It 's still in one piece .
Of course it is .
How 's your furniture going ?
I had to leave it .
A baby and power tools ...
You 'll find a way .
It 's your trade , what you like to do .
- Do you live here by yourself ? - Yeah .
But I 'm about to go .
What ?
Where ?
Where do you think ?
To the mountains .
So ...
Are you going alone ?
I guess .
I 'm my own home , right ?
Well ...
Congratulations .
Thanks .
And there 's a house ?
No ! There are only bushes .
But I plan to build something this year .
I 've missed you .
Campeon !
Hi , Dad !
Hey , stop !
- You look handsome . - I dusted off the suit .
- Why is Campeon downstairs ? - Can 't you see ? He 's freaked out .
The neighbors are complaining . So I brought him here .
Come in .
You look beautiful .
No sweets or TV or they won 't sleep .
Valeria , stop cracking your fingers .
You 'll end up all crooked .
In the refrigerator there is chicken and vegetables . Heat them up .
Here .
Remember , if anything happens , push this button .
The Neighborhood Watch will come to help you .
Have fun .
Best of luck with these two .
Behave yourselves . Don 't upset your aunt .
Be careful with the stairs .
Mom ...
- Be nice to your aunt . - Yes , goodbye .
Bye-bye .
- Do you want the flower , Jorge ? - Yes .
Go get the flower .
Get on the chair .
Aunty , I used the bathroom .
And there 's no water ?
I 'm coming , Pao .
Jorge , turn the volume down .
Hello ?
Yes , we 're watching a movie .
Everything is fine .
Yes , they 've had dinner .
Of course I heated it up , Mom !
Okay , okay .
I have to hang up , I 'll call you back .
Come here , boy . Come . What 's going on ?
What 's going on , boy ?
Turn it down , it 's too loud !
Jorge , stop it ! Give me the remote !
- Which one ? - Where did you put it ?
Look for it !
If you don 't give me the remote , we 're going to have a problem .
- Turn it down ! - Or what ? What are you going to do ?
- Don 't talk to me like that ! - " Don 't talk to me like that ! "
I 'm not playing ! Give me the remote now !
What if I don 't ? Are you going to throw me down the stairs ?
Like that child who ended up all dumb ?
No !
What 's wrong with you ? Let go !
- Let 's go , please ! - Are you out of your mind ?
It hurts !
Let 's go , please !
Let go of me !
What 's wrong with you , you moron ? I 'm going to call my mom !
Someone broke into the house !
Apparently he choked himself with the chain .
No one was there .
Nobody .
- I swear . Ask the kids ... - They can 't even talk .
Don 't worry .
If the lady felt in danger , it was good that she called us .
- Thanks . - No problem .
Dad ...
I swear ...
It 's okay , honey .
It 's okay .
Go to your grandma .
Let 's go .
- What did you do to them ? - What do you mean ?
Did you see Paola 's arm ?
She peed herself out of fear .
- Jorge has a sprained foot . - Someone broke into the house .
- Are you out of your mind ? - I swear .
This is the last time you get close to them .
People like you shouldn 't have children .
Are you serious ? You tell me that ?
When if it weren 't for our parents , you and your children would be on the street !
- Shut up ! - Fuck you and your aspirational life !
I hope one day Raul realizes how fucking fake you are !
- You shouldn 't have had children ! - Calm down !
- Fuck you ! Get the fuck out ! - I 'm out of here !
Go away !
- You believe me , don 't you ? - Of course I do .
Ursula told me if it didn 't work , there was another way .
What ?
You don 't think it could work ?
I got this in one of those rituals .
Sure it works , but you get into some pretty dark stuff .
Where are you going ?
Yes .
Thanks .
No . It 's all good .
Yes , we are here . Thank you .
Yeah ...
- And the apartment is yours ? - Yes , it is .
Well , It 's my mom 's , but we 're paying her for it .
It 's interesting , the wallpaper ...
- What about this ? - That was Valeria .
- She made everything . - I love it !
Very " do it yourself " from you .
- Well , let 's open that wine . - Please .
Are you okay ?
I talked to your mom .
But we 'll discuss this later .
- Hey . - Yes ?
I left the corkscrew on the table .
Marina , do you want some salad ? Give me your plate .
It 's my mom 's recipe .
Well , we are not very fond of eating with our hands ,
but these are really good .
Why advertising , Raul ?
You 've been doing that for years now , right ?
Yes .
We wanted to tell you that Brenda is no longer in the quartet .
She lacked passion . She was always complaining about staying late .
Well , she was actually afraid of public transportation at night .
When you are passionate about something , you find a way to do it .
I 'm so sorry .
Anyway , Raul ...
What I wanted to ask you is if you would like to ...
Excuse me for a moment .
It 's all good .
Val , what 's going on ?
Valeria . What 's that smell ?
Val ...
Get away from the door , damn it !
- It was a woman . - Valeria , come on !
It was a woman , she broke the cradle !
A fucking ghost woman ?
Are you listening to yourself ?
I know you didn 't spend the night at your parents ' .
How is Octavia doing ?
What about your niece and nephew ?
You weren 't going to tell me about that either ?
Yes .
You hurt the kids , you almost burned the fucking house down !
- I need your patience . - We 'll have to take other measures .
It 's a phase . It 's normal .
- We could commit her . - What are you saying ?
She 's pregnant !
Hello , darling .
What is happening to you is quite normal .
When you become a mother , you feel like you are split in two .
And wait for labor time !
You literally feel like your bones are breaking .
Of course you 're scared , honey .
I was terrified for a long time too .
The thing is you don 't go around telling everyone .
But
it 's worth it .
Mark my words .
Doesn 't that hurt the baby ?
No . It 's a common antidepressant prescribed in pregnancy .
It 's just a little help .
What do you think , Raul ?
We should try it .
Cheer up , Valeria . You 're just pregnant .
That 's all .
See you later .
Break a paw !
- A leg ! - It 's the same thing !
What is this ?
A neighbor gave it to me .
I found it in the baby 's room .
It 's for you !
" I can picture you .
You 're a wonderful dream .
I wait for you .
You 're the adventure of my lifetime .
I embrace you .
You 're the tenderness in my eyes .
I lull you .
You are the calm of my sleep and my hope upon awakening .
I look at you .
You 're the endearing landscape .
I 'll always take care of you ... My little one . "
Octavia !
Just breathe .
What are you doing ?
I think I want to be with you .
You think or do you really want to ?
Enough is enough ! Is this a game for you ?
I 'm sorry .
Look , go to your dreamy home with Raul .
- I 'll pass . - Stop trivializing me !
Really ?
You are the one who has been pretending for years
to be the one who grew up , the one who chose the right path .
- And the truth is you have no idea what you want . - And you do ?
Let 's see how you get on with your utopian tale of mountain life !
Go fuck yourself ! Get lost !
Valeria ! Valeria !
Step aside !
- Push ! Push ! - Breathe ! Breathe !
It won 't take long , Vale ! Let 's go !
Come on , push ! That 's it !
That 's it , we got her !
Here 's the princess .
Cut the cord .
We need to suture .
Nice !
Just a few stitches .
Congratulations .
Thanks .
Hello .
Look at her , Val .
Yeah !
- Valeria ... - What ?
Why won 't you look at her ?
I do look at her .
She 's just such a cute little thing .
I can 't leave you alone .
But you can 't cancel Marina again .
I won 't go .
Why don 't we call my mom ?
She has already helped us a lot . Let her rest .
What does this baby want ? She wants her boob ?
Does she want her boob ?
" Mom , I want my boob . "
Yes .
- You 're running late . - Yeah .
See you later .
Hello ?
Yes , don 't worry .
Okay , see you soon .
Thank you .
What are we doing here ?
Why did you bring her with you ?
I have to protect her .
From what ?
I have to do this .
What is happening to me has nothing to do with Raul .
It has nothing to do with you .
Please forgive me .
Forgive me Octavia .
Stop apologizing for everything .
Are you sure about this ?
Once it starts , there 's no turning back .
You 'll be fine .
Trust in them , Vale .
No , Chabe . You wait here .
You do have something nasty going on .
Can you help me ?
You are in deep shit , girl .
You really are .
Inside that place ,
this blanket is your child .
Bleed from the inside .
Bleed ... Bleed from the inside .
- Stab her ! Stab her ! - Get out ! Get out !
- Stab her !
- Get out ! - Get out !
Here .
Vale ...